A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1981-1990 FA402
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1987; 0.37 Cubic Feet 28 microfilm reels (35mm); 28 Reels 28 microfilm reels (35mm)
  - England, 1987; 1987/401
    - University of Bath (Room, Graham), 1987 (Reel 19, Frame 723)
    - B-W, 1987 (Reel 20, Frame 1)
    - England - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1987; 1987/401.E
      - Carter, Simon, 1987 (Reel 20, Frame 546)
  - Ireland, 1987; 1987/403
    - Northern Ireland Voluntary Trust (Cook, David), 1987 (Reel 20, Frame 552)
  - Scotland, 1987; 1987/405
    - H-K, 1987 (Reel 20, Frame 603)
  - Wales, 1987; 1987/407
    - Baker, Colin, 1987 (Reel 20, Frame 633)
  - Australia, 1987; 1987/410
    - D-M, 1987 (Reel 20, Frame 641)
  - Canada, 1987; 1987/427
    - A-Y, 1987 (Reel 20, Frame 647)
    - Canada - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1987; 1987/427.E
      - Mackenzie, Fiona, 1987 (Reel 21, Frame 1)
  - Jamaica, 1987; 1987/437
    - Ashley, D., 1987 (Reel 21, Frame 7)
  - Ceylon, 1987; 1987/462
    - Suriyakumaran, C., 1987 (Reel 21, Frame 10)
  - Hong Kong, 1987; 1987/463
    - Beijing-Hong Kong Academic Exchange Centre, 1987 (Reel 21, Frame 23)
  - India, 1987; 1987/464
    - B-U, 1987 (Reel 21, Frame 29)
  - Pakistan, 1987; 1987/465
    - Salam, Abdus, 1987 (Reel 21, Frame 101)
  - Bengal/Bangladesh, 1987; 1987/466
    - International Centre for Diarrhoeal Disease Research, Bangladesh, 1987 (Reel 21, Frame 107)
  - Malaysia, 1987; 1987/473
    - I-U, 1987 (Reel 21, Frame 146)
  - Africa, 1987; 1987/475
    - Association of Faculties of Agriculture in Africa, 1987 (Reel 21, Frame 172)
  - Kenya, 1987; 1987/476
    - A-W, 1987 (Reel 21, Frame 188)
    - Kenya - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1987; 1987/476.E
      - Anyango, Beatrice, 1987 (Reel 21, Frame 301)
  - East Africa Region, 1987; 1987/477
    - O-U, 1987 (Reel 21, Frame 305)
  - South Africa Region, 1987; 1987/487
    - Norman, David W., 1987 (Reel 21, Frame 311)
  - Cape of Good Hope, 1987; 1987/489
    - A-W, 1987 (Reel 21, Frame 316)
  - Uganda, 1987; 1987/492
    - B-U, 1987 (Reel 21, Frame 423)
  - West Africa, 1987; 1987/495
    - N-W, 1987 (Reel 21, Frame 437)
  - Ghana (Gold Coast), 1987; 1987/496
    - L-M, 1987 (Reel 21, Frame 483)
  - Nigeria, 1987; 1987/497
    - B-U, 1987 (Reel 21, Frame 492)
    - Nigeria - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1987; 1987/497.E
      - Nwagwu, Mark, 1987 (Reel 21, Frame 514)
  - Sierra Leone, 1987; 1987/499
    - Monde, Sama S., 1987 (Reel 21, Frame 561)
  - France, 1987; 1987/500
    - C-R, 1987 (Reel 21, Frame 571)
  - Ivory Coast, 1987; 1987/527
    - Agriculture, 1987 (Reel 21, Frame 610)
  - Tunis, 1987; 1987/539
    Tunisia
    - International Cultural Center, Tunisia (Chouchane, Fred), 1987 (Reel 21, Frame 853)
  - People's Republic of China, 1987; 1987/601
    - C-Z, 1987 (Reel 22, Frame 1)
    - People's Republic of China - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1987; 1987/601.E
      - Feng Zhijie, 1987 (Reel 22, Frame 77)
  - Japan, 1987; 1987/609
    - H-T, 1987 (Reel 22, Frame 81)
  - Korea, 1987; 1987/613
    - Kim, Don Soo, 1987 (Reel 22, Frame 201)
    - Korea - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1987; 1987/613.E
      - Oh, Sung Jong, 1987 (Reel 22, Frame 203)
  - Thailand, 1987; 1987/617
    - C-T, 1987 (Reel 22, Frame 293)
  - Holland, 1987; 1987/650
    - D-W, 1987 (Reel 22, Frame 297)
  - Indonesia, 1987; 1987/652
    - H-U, 1987 (Reel 22, Frame 439)
  - Foundation for Agricultural Plant Breeding, 1987; 1987/670
    - Foundation for Agricultural Plant Breeding, 1987 (Reel 22, Frame 448)
  - Europe, 1987; 1987/700
    - Council of Europe, 1987 (Reel 22, Frame 452)
  - Ethiopia, 1987; 1987/701
    - Wilson, R. T., 1987 (Reel 22, Frame 466)
  - Austria, 1987; 1987/705
    - D-I, 1987 (Reel 22, Frame 503)
  - Belgium, 1987; 1987/707
    - University of Ghent (I.R.R.I.B.T. Toxin Genes), 1987 (Reel 22, Frame 558)
  - Belgian Congo, 1987; 1987/709
    - N-U, 1987 (Reel 22, Frame 573)
  - Bulgaria, 1987; 1987/711
    Bulgaria
    - Lyudmila Zhivokova International Foundation, 1987 (Reel 22, Frame 580)
  - Germany, 1987; 1987/717
    - A-M, 1987 (Reel 22, Frame 584)
  - Tanganyika, 1987; 1987/723
    - M-N, 1987 (Reel 22, Frame 592)
  - Italy, 1987; 1987/751
    - B-W, 1987 (Reel 22, Frame 631)
  - Finland, 1987; 1987/787
    - E, 1987 (Reel 22, Frame 651)
  - Poland, 1987; 1987/789
    - D, 1987 (Reel 22, Frame 654)
  - Spain, 1987; 1987/795
    - I-U, 1987 (Reel 22, Frame 674)
  - Sweden, 1987; 1987/800
    - B-S, 1987 (Reel 22, Frame 683)
  - Switzerland, 1987; 1987/803
    - S, 1987 (Reel 22, Frame 688)
  - Saudi Arabia and Oman, 1987; 1987/817
    Saudi Arabia; Oman
    - King Feisal International Prize, 1987 (Reel 22, Frame 755)
  - Palestine/Israel, 1987; 1987/825
    - B-W, 1987 (Reel 22, Frame 770)
  - Lebanon, 1987; 1987/833
    - Beirut University College, 1987 (Reel 22, Frame 822)
  - Special Interests and Explorations (SIE) - Biotechnology Career Fellowships, 1987; 1987/860
    - H-R, 1987 (Reel 22, Frame 826)
  - Members and Meetings, 1987; 1987/903
    - D-W, 1987 (Reel 22, Frame 838)
  - Humanities, 1987; 1987/911
    - Humanities - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1987; 1987/911.E
      - A-C, 1987 (Reel 23, Frame 1)
      - Harvard University (Resident Fellows), 1987 (Reel 23, Frame 571)
      - F-H, 1987 (Reel 23, Frame 691)
      - I-N, 1987 (Reel 24, Frame 1)
      - State University of New York at Binghamton (Resident Fellows), 1987 (Reel 24, Frame 292)
      - State University of New York (B-S), 1987 (Reel 24, Frame 730)
      - R-S, 1987 (Reel 25, Frame 1)
      - Tulane University (Resident Fellows), 1987 (Reel 25, Frame 585)
      - University (C-H), 1987 (Reel 25, Frame 669)
      - University (I), 1987 (Reel 26, Frame 1)
      - University of Kentucky (Resident Fellows), 1987 (Reel 26, Frame 256)
      - University (M), 1987 (Reel 26, Frame 628)
      - University (N-P), 1987 (Reel 27, Frame 1)
      - V-W, 1987 (Reel 27, Frame 638)
      - Y, 1987 (Reel 28, Frame 1)
  - Great Neglected Diseases (GND)/Health Sciences (HS), 1987; 1987/928
    - Great Neglected Diseases (GND)/Health Sciences (HS) - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1987; 1987/928.E
      - Salzman, Andrew, 1987 (Reel 28, Frame 286)
  - Arts and Humanities, 1987; 1987/929
    - Staff Position Search (G-M), 1987 (Reel 28, Frame 291)
- General Correspondence, 1988; 0.4 Cubic Feet 30 microfilm reels (35mm); 30 Reels 30 microfilm reels (35mm)
  - International, 1988; 1988/100
    - Goldmark, Peter C., 1988 (Reel 1, Frame 1)
    - Lyman, Richard W., 1988 (Reel 1, Frame 378)
    - Lynam, John, 1988 (Reel 1, Frame 419)
    - A-F, 1988 (Reel 1, Frame 422)
    - H-K, 1988 (Reel 1, Frame 532)
    - L-W, 1988 (Reel 1, Frame 639)
  - International Organizations, 1988; 1988/103
    - United Nations, World Health Organization (A-S), 1988 (Reel 2, Frame 1)
    - United Nations Development Programme (B-R), 1988 (Reel 2, Frame 465)
    - United Nations Fund for Population Activities (Sadik, Nafis), 1988 (Reel 2, Frame 500)
    - United Nations Industrial Development Organization, 1988 (Reel 2, Frame 666)
    - United Nations International Children's Emergency Fund (Facts for Life), 1988 (Reel 2, Frame 732)
    - United Nations Latin American Institute for Crime Prevention and Treatment of Offenders, 1988 (Reel 2, Frame 795)
    - A-H, 1988 (Reel 2, Frame 798)
    - I, 1988 (Reel 3, Frame 1)
    - S-W, 1988 (Reel 3, Frame 248)
  - CIAT (International Center for Tropical Agriculture), 1988; 1988/110
    - 110, 1988 (Reel 3, Frame 534)
  - IITA (International Institute of Tropical Agriculture - Nigeria), 1988; 1988/115
    - 115, 1988 (Reel 3, Frame 558)
  - Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 1988; 1988/120
    - Marx, Gary T., 1988 (Reel 3, Frame 572)
  - Greater Voice for Africa in the United States (Africa Policy Watch Project), 1988; 1988/121
    - A-U, 1988 (Reel 3, Frame 601)
  - Conflict in International Relations, 1988; 1988/155
    - Wilgesprint Fellowship Centre (Port Elizabeth Self Help Development Association), 1988 (Reel 3, Frame 872)
  - United States of America, 1988; 1988/200
    - American (A-I), 1988 (Reel 4, Frame 1)
    - American Journal of Agricultural Economics, 1988 (Reel 4, Frame 267)
    - American (P-S), 1988 (Reel 4, Frame 477)
    - Ab-Ar, 1988 (Reel 4, Frame 491)
    - As, 1988 (Reel 4, Frame 712)
    - B, 1988 (Reel 5, Frame 1)
    - Casey Foundation, 1988 (Reel 5, Frame 501)
    - Ca, 1988 (Reel 5, Frame 726)
    - Center (A-W), 1988 (Reel 6, Frame 1)
    - Ce, 1988 (Reel 6, Frame 254)
    - Chandler, Robert Flint, Jr., 1988 (Reel 6, Frame 350)
    - Ch-Ci, 1988 (Reel 6, Frame 464)
    - Cl-Com, 1988 (Reel 7, Frame 1)
    - Council (C-S), 1988 (Reel 7, Frame 610)
    - Con-Cu, 1988 (Reel 8, Frame 1)
    - D, 1988 (Reel 8, Frame 330)
    - E, 1988 (Reel 8, Frame 648)
    - F, 1988 (Reel 9, Frame 1)
    - Grant Foundation, 1988 (Reel 9, Frame 459)
    - G, 1988 (Reel 9, Frame 472)
    - Harvard University (E-V), 1988 (Reel 10, Frame 1)
    - H, 1988 (Reel 10, Frame 153)
    - I, 1988 (Reel 10, Frame 585)
    - J-K, 1988 (Reel 11, Frame 1)
    - L, 1988 (Reel 11, Frame 444)
    - M, 1988 (Reel 12, Frame 1)
    - National (A-C), 1988 (Reel 12, Frame 622)
    - National Council of LaRaza (Yzaguirre), 1988 (Reel 13, Frame 0.001)
    - National (E-W), 1988 (Reel 13, Frame 1)
    - New (A-W), 1988 (Reel 13, Frame 288)
    - New York City, Education (G-J), 1988 (Reel 13, Frame 691)
    - New York (A-U), 1988 (Reel 14, Frame 1)
    - N, 1988 (Reel 14, Frame 227)
    - O, 1988 (Reel 14, Frame 346)
    - Pa-Pl, 1988 (Reel 14, Frame 606)
    - Port Authority of New York and New Jersey (Schwartz), 1988 (Reel 15, Frame 1)
    - Po-Pr, 1988 (Reel 015A, Frame 1)
    - Pu-Q, 1988 (Reel 015A, Frame 319)
    - Rockefeller, 1988 (Reel 015A, Frame 595)
    - R, 1988 (Reel 015A, Frame 605)
    - Po-Pr, 1988 (Reel 015A, Frame 1)
    - Pu-Q, 1988 (Reel 015A, Frame 319)
    - Rockefeller, 1988 (Reel 015A, Frame 595)
    - R, 1988 (Reel 015A, Frame 605)
    - Sa-Si, 1988 (Reel 16, Frame 1)
    - Sl-Sy, 1988 (Reel 16, Frame 315)
    - Technoserve, Inc., 1988 (Reel 16, Frame 734)
    - T, 1988 (Reel 17, Frame 1)
    - United States (A-S), 1988 (Reel 17, Frame 169)
    - United States Information Agency, 1988 (Reel 17, Frame 243)
    - United States Institute of Peace, 1988 (Reel 17, Frame 292)
    - United States Postal Service (Frank, Anthony M.), 1988 (Reel 17, Frame 295)
    - University of California (A-S), 1988 (Reel 17, Frame 317)
    - University of California (R-W), 1988 (Reel 17, Frame 753)
    - University (A-I), 1988 (Reel 18, Frame 1)
    - University (M), 1988 (Reel 18, Frame 326)
    - University (N-W), 1988 (Reel 18, Frame 615)
    - U, 1988 (Reel 18, Frame 887)
    - V-Wh, 1988 (Reel 19, Frame 1)
    - Wi, 1988 (Reel 19, Frame 380)
    - Wo-Wy, 1988 (Reel 19, Frame 596)
    - Y-Z, 1988 (Reel 19, Frame 776)
    - United States of America - Medical Sciences, 1988; 1988/200.A
      - University of California (Medical Schools), 1988 (Reel 20, Frame 1)
    - United States of America - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1988; 1988/200.D
      - Winrock International Institute for Agriculture Development, Future U.S. Development Assistance (Colloquium), 1988 (Reel 20, Frame 11)
    - United States of America - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1988; 1988/200.E
      - Grosz-Ngate, Maria, 1988 (Reel 20, Frame 22)
  - Philippines, 1988; 1988/242
    - C-T, 1988 (Reel 20, Frame 42)
  - Puerto Rico, 1988; 1988/243
    - F-U, 1988 (Reel 20, Frame 106)
  - Fellowships for American Playwrights/Playwrights-in-Residence Program, 1988; 1988/272
    - C-J, 1988 (Reel 20, Frame 117)
  - Argentina, 1988; 1988/301
    - A, 1988 (Reel 20, Frame 203)
  - Brazil, 1988; 1988/305
    - B-C, 1988 (Reel 20, Frame 226)
  - Chile, 1988; 1988/309
    - C-Z, 1988 (Reel 20, Frame 243)
  - Colombia, 1988; 1988/311
    - T-U, 1988 (Reel 20, Frame 411)
  - Costa Rica, 1988; 1988/313
    - A-N, 1988 (Reel 20, Frame 418)
  - Cuba, 1988; 1988/315
    - Vilasis, Mayra, 1988 (Reel 20, Frame 455)
  - Guatemala, 1988; 1988/319
    Guatemala
    - Centro Universitario de Peten, 1988 (Reel 20, Frame 458)
  - Honduras, 1988; 1988/321
    - Escuela Agricola Panamericana (Andrews, Keith L.), 1988 (Reel 20, Frame 462)
  - Mexico, 1988; 1988/323
    - B-O, 1988 (Reel 20, Frame 509)
  - Peru, 1988; 1988/331
    - Brown, Kenneth J., 1988 (Reel 20, Frame 579)
  - Dominican Republic, 1988; 1988/335
    - Asociacion para el Desarrolla, Inc., 1988 (Reel 20, Frame 602)
  - Venezuela, 1988; 1988/339
    - Venezuelan Foundation for the Conservation of Biological Diversity, 1988 (Reel 20, Frame 688)
  - England, 1988; 1988/401
    - A-G, 1988 (Reel 20, Frame 715)
    - University (B-S), 1988 (Reel 21, Frame 1)
    - I-W, 1988 (Reel 21, Frame 456)
  - Ireland, 1988; 1988/403
    - Ireland - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1988; 1988/403.D
      - Agriculture (Ross, Malcolm), 1988 (Reel 21, Frame 579)
  - Scotland, 1988; 1988/405
    - Institute of Terrestrial Ecology (Leakey, R. R. B.), 1988 (Reel 21, Frame 616)
  - Wales, 1988; 1988/407
    - University College (Cardiff), 1988 (Reel 21, Frame 624)
  - Australia, 1988; 1988/410
    - C-U, 1988 (Reel 21, Frame 626)
  - Caribbean Region and Central America, including Netherlands Antilles, 1988; 1988/420
    - Foundation for Management Education in Central America (Trowbridge, Alexander B.), 1988 (Reel 21, Frame 658)
  - Canada, 1988; 1988/427
    - C-M, 1988 (Reel 21, Frame 691)
  - Hong Kong, 1988; 1988/463
    - Yee, Albert H., 1988 (Reel 21, Frame 831)
  - India, 1988; 1988/464
    - B-V, 1988 (Reel 22, Frame 1)
  - Pakistan, 1988; 1988/465
    - A-H, 1988 (Reel 22, Frame 244)
  - Bengal / Bangladesh, 1988; 1988/466
    - International Center for Diarrhoeal Disease Research, Bangladesh, 1988 (Reel 22, Frame 250)
  - Malaysia, 1988; 1988/473
    - Statistics, 1988 (Reel 22, Frame 271)
  - West Africa, 1988; 1988/495
    - Prudencio, Yves Coffi, 1988 (Reel 23, Frame 1)
    - B-W, 1988 (Reel 23, Frame 122)
  - Ghana (Gold Coast), 1988; 1988/496
    - Venkatcharya, K., 1988 (Reel 23, Frame 211)
  - Nigeria, 1988; 1988/497
    - Nigeria - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1988; 1988/497.E
      - Awoniyi, Caleb A., 1988 (Reel 23, Frame 318)
      - A-U, 1988 (Reel 23, Frame 241)
  - France, 1988; 1988/500
    - F-W, 1988 (Reel 23, Frame 356)
  - French Guinea, 1988; 1988/525
    - Klitgaard, Robert, 1988 (Reel 23, Frame 415)
  - Ivory Coast, 1988; 1988/527
    - African Development Bank (Okelo, E. M.), 1988 (Reel 23, Frame 422)
  - Senegal, 1988; 1988/531
    - Collion, Marie-Helene, 1988 (Reel 23, Frame 437)
  - People's Republic of China, 1988; 1988/601
    - C-X, 1988 (Reel 23, Frame 442)
  - Macao, 1988; 1988/602
    Macau
    - Wilson, Patricia, 1988 (Reel 23, Frame 699)
  - Taiwan, 1988; 1988/605
    - Asian Vegetable Research and Development, 1988 (Reel 23, Frame 705)
  - Japan, 1988; 1988/609
    - A-T, 1988 (Reel 23, Frame 718)
  - Korea, 1988; 1988/613
    - Korea Sericultural Association, 1988 (Reel 23, Frame 949)
  - Thailand, 1988; 1988/617
    - C-W, 1988 (Reel 24, Frame 1)
  - Holland, 1988; 1988/650
    - B-V, 1988 (Reel 24, Frame 113)
  - Indonesia, 1988; 1988/652
    - C-N, 1988 (Reel 24, Frame 222)
  - Ethiopia, 1988; 1988/701
    - Wilson, R. T., 1988 (Reel 24, Frame 301)
  - Belgium, 1988; 1988/707
    - A-T, 1988 (Reel 24, Frame 341)
  - Denmark, 1988; 1988/713
    - Riso National Laboratory, 1988 (Reel 24, Frame 463)
  - Germany, 1988; 1988/717
    - B-N, 1988 (Reel 24, Frame 465)
  - Greece, 1988; 1988/749
    - Antzoulatou-Retsila, Eurydice, 1988 (Reel 24, Frame 478)
  - Russia, 1988; 1988/785
    - Leonov, Boris, 1988 (Reel 24, Frame 491)
  - Poland, 1988; 1988/789
    - Januszewicz, Wlodimierz, 1988 (Reel 24, Frame 554)
  - Spain, 1988; 1988/795
    - Teatro Guirigai, 1988 (Reel 24, Frame 560)
  - Sweden, 1988; 1988/800
    - C-S, 1988 (Reel 24, Frame 598)
  - Switzerland, 1988; 1988/803
    - C-S, 1988 (Reel 24, Frame 682)
  - Turkey, 1988; 1988/805
    - Iman, I. Hakki, 1988 (Reel 24, Frame 709)
  - Cyprus, 1988; 1988/809
    Cyprus
    - Cyprus American Archaeological Research Institute, 1988 (Reel 24, Frame 713)
  - Egypt, 1988; 1988/812
    - Cairo Demographic Center, 1988 (Reel 24, Frame 750)
  - Palestine / Israel, 1988; 1988/825
    - Hebrew University (Kagan, Yair), 1988 (Reel 24, Frame 758)
  - Lebanon, 1988; 1988/833
    - A-B, 1988 (Reel 24, Frame 761)
  - Special Interests and Explorations (SIE) - Biotechnology Career Fellowships, 1988; 1988/860
    - Hertig, Cecilia Margarita, 1988 (Reel 24, Frame 797)
  - Members and Meetings, 1988; 1988/903
    - G-W, 1988 (Reel 24, Frame 815)
  - Humanities, 1988; 1988/911
    - Humanities - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1988; 1988/911.E
      - A-Bal, 1988 (Reel 25, Frame 1)
      - Baylor University (Resident Fellows), 1988 (Reel 25, Frame 148)
      - Columbia University, Resident Fellows (B-S), 1988 (Reel 25, Frame 524)
      - C-G, 1988 (Reel 25, Frame 823)
      - Harvard University (Resident Fellows), 1988 (Reel 26, Frame 1)
      - Marquette University (Resident Fellows), 1988 (Reel 26, Frame 101)
      - Michigan State University (Resident Fellows), 1988 (Reel 26, Frame 215)
      - Music Research Institute (Resident Fellows), 1988 (Reel 26, Frame 611)
      - Ohio State University (Resident Fellows), 1988 (Reel 26, Frame 789)
      - Smith College (Resident Fellows), 1988 (Reel 26, Frame 857)
      - State University of New York, Binghamton, 1988 (Reel 26, Frame 940)
      - State University of New York at Stony Brook, 1988 (Reel 27, Frame 1)
      - Syracuse University (Resident Fellows), 1988 (Reel 27, Frame 164)
      - University of Massachusetts (Resident Fellows), 1988 (Reel 27, Frame 296)
      - University of Minnesota, Resident Fellows, 1988 (Reel 27, Frame 602)
      - University of Mississippi (Resident Fellows), 1988 (Reel 27, Frame 718)
      - University of New Mexico, Resident Fellows, 1988 (Reel 27, Frame 805)
      - University of Oregon (Resident Fellows), 1988 (Reel 28, Frame 1)
      - University of Pennsylvania, Resident Fellows, 1988 (Reel 28, Frame 130)
      - University of Pittsburgh, Resident Fellows (F-S), 1988 (Reel 28, Frame 313)
      - University of South Carolina (Resident Fellows), 1988 (Reel 28, Frame 688)
      - University (C-T), Resident Fellows (Declinations), 1988 (Reel 29, Frame 1)
      - University of Wisconsin, Resident Fellows (H), 1988 (Reel 29, Frame 280)
      - Williams College (Resident Fellows), 1988 (Reel 29, Frame 659)
      - Staff Position Search, 1988 (Reel 29, Frame 947)
- General Correspondence, 1989; 0.5 Cubic Feet 38 microfilm reels (35mm); 38 Reels 38 microfilm reels (35mm)
  - International, 1989; 1989/100
    - Goldmark, Peter C., Jr. (Speeches), 1989 (Reel 1, Frame 1)
    - B-Y, 1989 (Reel 1, Frame 323)
  - International Organizations, 1989; 1989/103
    - United Nations (D-W), 1989 (Reel 1, Frame 707)
    - United Nations Center for Human Settlements, 1989 (Reel 1, Frame 850)
    - United Nations Development Programme, 1989 (Reel 1, Frame 855)
    - United Nations Educational Scientific and Cultural Organization, 1989 (Reel 2, Frame 1)
    - United Nations Fund for Populations Activities (Janitschek, Hans W.), 1989 (Reel 2, Frame 88)
    - United Nations High Commission for Refugees, 1989 (Reel 2, Frame 138)
    - United Nations Industrial Development Organization, 1989 (Reel 2, Frame 148)
    - United Nations International Children's Emergency Fund (C-P), 1989 (Reel 2, Frame 151)
    - C, 1989 (Reel 2, Frame 218)
    - I, 1989 (Reel 2, Frame 291)
    - R-W, 1989 (Reel 2, Frame 677)
  - IPP (International Potato Program), 1989; 1989/107
    - International Potato Program, 1989 (Reel 3, Frame 1)
  - International Center for Agricultural Research in the Dry Areas, 1989; 1989/118
    - International Center for Agricultural Research in the Dry Areas, 1989 (Reel 3, Frame 14)
  - Greater Voice for Africa in the United States (Africy Policy Watch Project), 1989; 1989/121
    - Greater Voice for Africa in the United States (Africa Policy Watch Project), 1989 (Reel 3, Frame 58)
    - A-C, 1989 (Reel 3, Frame 146)
    - J-U, 1989 (Reel 3, Frame 759)
  - Conflict in International Relations, 1989; 1989/155
    - Wilgesprint Fellowship Center (Port Elizabeth Self Help), 1989 (Reel 4, Frame 1)
  - United States of America, 1989; 1989/200
    - Ab-Ag, 1989 (Reel 4, Frame 6)
    - American (A-J), 1989 (Reel 4, Frame 161)
    - American (L-S), 1989 (Reel 4, Frame 669)
    - American Public Radio - Volume 1, Number 2, 1989; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15955)
    - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies (M-S), 1989 (Reel 4, Frame 748)
    - Am-Au, 1989 (Reel 5, Frame 1)
    - B-Bo, 1989 (Reel 5, Frame 364)
    - Br-Bu, 1989 (Reel 6, Frame 1)
    - Cab-Cam, 1989 (Reel 6, Frame 402)
    - Carnegie (C-M), 1989 (Reel 7, Frame 1)
    - Cap-Cat, 1989 (Reel 7, Frame 210)
    - Center (A-C), 1989 (Reel 7, Frame 503)
    - Center (E-U), 1989 (Reel 8, Frame 1)
    - Ch, 1989 (Reel 8, Frame 346)
    - Ci, 1989 (Reel 8, Frame 608)
    - Cl, 1989 (Reel 9, Frame 1)
    - Coa-Com, 1989 (Reel 9, Frame 152)
    - Con-Cot, 1989 (Reel 9, Frame 605)
    - Cou-Cov, 1989 (Reel 10, Frame 1)
    - Cr-Cu, 1989 (Reel 10, Frame 279)
    - D, 1989 (Reel 10, Frame 671)
    - Education Commission of the States (Anderson, Beverly L.), 1989 (Reel 11, Frame 1)
    - Eisenhower Foundation, 1989 (Reel 11, Frame 104)
    - E, 1989 (Reel 11, Frame 309)
    - Fa-Fi, 1989 (Reel 11, Frame 582)
    - Fo-Fu, 1989 (Reel 11, Frame 717)
      - The New American Orchestra - "Jazz Alive" Hour 1, 1983 May; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15956)
      - The New American Orchestra - "Jazz Alive" Hour 2, 1983 May; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15957)
    - Ga-Go, 1989 (Reel 12, Frame 1)
    - Gr-Gu, 1989 (Reel 12, Frame 275)
    - Ha, 1989 (Reel 12, Frame 660)
    - He-Hi, 1989 (Reel 13, Frame 1)
    - Ho-Hy, 1989 (Reel 13, Frame 376)
    - Institute (C-R), 1989 (Reel 13, Frame 750)
    - International (B-R), 1989 (Reel 14, Frame 1)
    - I, 1989 (Reel 14, Frame 197)
    - J, 1989 (Reel 14, Frame 650)
    - K, 1989 (Reel 15, Frame 1)
    - La-Le, 1989 (Reel 15, Frame 163)
    - Li-Lu, 1989 (Reel 15, Frame 457)
    - M-Me, 1989 (Reel 16, Frame 1)
    - Mi, 1989 (Reel 16, Frame 481)
    - Mo-My, 1989 (Reel 17, Frame 1)
    - National Academy (P-S), 1989 (Reel 17, Frame 287)
    - National Association (A-S), 1989 (Reel 17, Frame 599)
    - National (A-Ce), 1989 (Reel 18, Frame 1)
    - National (Com-Cou), 1989 (Reel 18, Frame 415)
    - National (E-G), 1989 (Reel 19, Frame 1)
    - National (H-I), 1989 (Reel 20, Frame 1)
    - National (L-R), 1989 (Reel 20, Frame 272)
    - National (U-Y), 1989 (Reel 20, Frame 605)
    - New (E-W), 1989 (Reel 21, Frame 1)
    - New York (A-R), 1989 (Reel 21, Frame 293)
    - New York (S-U), 1989 (Reel 21, Frame 651)
    - N, 1989 (Reel 22, Frame 1)
    - O, 1989 (Reel 22, Frame 185)
    - Pan American Health Organization (February - June), 1989 (Reel 22, Frame 408)
    - Pan American Health Organization (August - October), 1989 (Reel 23, Frame 1)
    - People for the American Way, 1989 (Reel 23, Frame 478)
    - Pa-Pi, 1989 (Reel 24, Frame 1)
    - Pl-Po, 1989 (Reel 24, Frame 337)
    - Pr, 1989 (Reel 24, Frame 586)
    - Pu-Q, 1989 (Reel 25, Frame 1)
    - Ra-Re, 1989 (Reel 25, Frame 396)
    - Rockefeller, 1989 (Reel 25, Frame 827)
    - Ri-Ru, 1989 (Reel 26, Frame 1)
    - Sa-Si, 1989 (Reel 26, Frame 162)
    - Sk-So, 1989 (Reel 26, Frame 398)
    - Sp-Sy, 1989 (Reel 26, Frame 669)
    - Technoserve, Inc., 1989 (Reel 27, Frame 1)
    - T, 1989 (Reel 27, Frame 118)
    - United States (A-S), 1989 (Reel 27, Frame 616)